auctionsoftwarereview.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy | The Auction Software Review

This Privacy Policy covers The Auction Software Review's treatment of personally identifiable information that is collected when you are on the site.

## Information Collection and Use

  * The Auction Software Review collects personally identifiable information when you register for a member account, complete feedback forms, and make submissions to the site
  * When you register with The Auction Software Review, we ask for a member name and email address.
  * Payment details for any pay services are supplied via PayPal and are not stored on this web site in any form.
  * The Auction Software Review automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address and the page you requested
  * The Auction Software Review uses this information to customise the content you see, to fulfil your requests for services, and to contact you with information you have requested

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

The Auction Software Review will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone, unless required by law. 

## Cookies

  * The Auction Software Review may set and access cookies on your computer
  * Other web sites do not have access to The Auction Software Review's cookies

| **Cookie name** | **Purpose** | **More information**  
---|---|---  
ASPSESSIONID* | Used so users can login to the site.  |    
cookieTest | Used to test if cookies are enabled in the user's browser. |    
CountryCode | Used to personalise content to the user's country (looked up anonymously using IP address)  |    
email  
LoginToken  
memberName   
|  Used to remember users so they do not need to enter their login details the next time they come to the site. | Duration to remain logged in can be modified on the profile page.   
screenSize | Used to remember the preferred forum input text box size selected by the user  |    
  
Google Analytics  
_utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmv  
_utmz

|  Used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in anonymously, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  | [Google Analytics ](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)  
  
## Editing and Deleting Your Member Information

  * You may edit your member information at any time by going to the Profile page
  * You may request deletion of your member details by sending an email quoting the email address you registered with

## Security

  * Your member information is password-protected for your privacy and security
  * Your password is stored in encrypted form
  * Payment details provided for any pay services are not stored on this web site in any form

## Third-Party Advertising 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit The Auction Software Review. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For more information about this practice and to opt out of having this information used by these companies see the following:

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Auction Software Review may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our home page.
